Falcons somehow one step ahead.
猎鹰不知怎么又提前一步。
All the staging, all the signs pointed towards the A play.
前面的铺垫和信号，全都像是在指向 A 点。
karrigan had his pieces in the right place.
大表哥 也早就把人摆在了正确位置。
It's now a chance at another OT.
现在又有机会拖进加时。
Falcons had two chances in regulation they couldn't close.
猎鹰 在常规时间里有两次结束比赛的机会，但都没能把握住。
This is FURIA's second chance all the same.
而 黑豹 这边，同样迎来了第二次机会。
They play it together.
他们聚在一起
KSCERATO in lobby. FURIA walk outside.
KSCERATO 留在黄房，FURIA 这边往外场走。
This is a fight between m0NESY and molodoy.
这一波，像是 m0NESY 和 molodoy 的正面对决。
We might get to see it in round 30.
第 30 回合，真可能就在这里见分晓。
The damage done on YEKINDAR.
YEKINDAR 先被打出伤害。
That's your aggressive lurker brought down so low.
这个负责前顶和单摸的人，血量已经被压得很低了。
They just want this fight. They just want this pick.
他们就是想强行接这波枪，想先抓一个。
m0NESY's not giving it.
但 m0NESY 不给这个机会。
Oh, NiKo nearly punished. Will get gun on in time.
NiKo 差一点被逮到机，不过Niko还是架住了枪。
YEKINDAR cleaned up. The early advantage going the way of Falcons.
YEKINDAR 被收掉，前期优势已经倒向 Falcons。
Almost made it down, but so has kyousuke.
差一点就能下到下层，但 kyousuke 也已经同步跟到了。
The yard hit has to come now.
外场这波必须现在就打了。
FalleN wrestling back a kill here on this main lurk.
FalleN 在正门单摸这边，硬是扳回了一个人头。
Clashing with his captain counterpart.
他对上的，正是另一边的指挥位。
Bomb still being played forward into lower.
炸弹这边，还是在往下层推进。
molodoy's been spotted. It's the info on the early rotate out of kyousuke.
molodoy 已经被看到了，这条信息也让 kyousuke 提前开始转点。
They're gonna try and end this upper.
他们想直接从上层把这回合结束掉。
FalleN right now is taking space away in heaven.
而 FalleN 这会儿还在天堂位继续抢空间。
This is a crazy move. This is a wild call.
这波动作太疯狂了，这个决策也太大胆了。
It all hinges on KSCERATO and FalleN at this top site.
上层这边，胜负现在几乎就压在 KSCERATO 和 FalleN 身上。
TeSeS has the info, sees them in the vents.
TeSeS 已经拿到信息了，也看到了通风管里的人。
Can guess what's coming his way.
他已经能猜到接下来要发生什么。
KSCERATO shuts him down.
KSCERATO 直接把他打掉。
And that top site cracked wide open.
上层防线一下就被撕开了。
Falcons have had some miraculous rounds,
Falcons 前面已经打出过几次神奇回合了，
but right now kyousuke and m0NESY have got to summon something else.
但现在，kyousuke 和 m0NESY 还得再拿出点更夸张的东西。
First kill goes m0NESY's way.
m0NESY先拿下第一个人头
Hands off the keyboard. No one move a muscle.
现在谁都别乱动，手都先离开键盘。
Time will do the heavy lifting.
接下来，时间会替他们做大部分工作。
Time will solve this for us.
时间会替他们把问题解决掉。
Time is all we need. How many times have we heard that?
他们现在最需要的就是时间。这话我们都听过多少次了。
kyousuke looking for that first incision.
kyousuke 在找第一个突破口。
Finds yuurih back at the site.
他先在包点后方逮到了 yuurih。
Brazilians getting picked apart.
黑豹正在被逐个击破。
And it ends up with this: m0NESY top performer.
最后就打成了这样，m0NESY 成了全场最关键的人。
FalleN dead. The captain brushed aside.
FalleN 倒下，指挥被直接清掉。
A nail-biter of a defuse that just comes in.
最后这个拆包，惊险到了极点。
m0NESY is magic.
孩神神了！